Board of Governors fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Agenda support papers, 1963 - 2003; F-33-2; 15.83 m of textual records
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Mar. 1970, F-33-2-0-0-145 (Archival box - standard 33-26)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Mar. 1970, F-33-2-0-0-146 (Archival box - standard 33-26)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Mar. 1970, F-33-2-0-0-147 (Archival box - standard 33-27)
  - Agenda support papers 1/4. Apr. 1970, F-33-2-0-0-148 (Archival box - standard 33-27)
  - Agenda support papers 2/4. Apr. 1970, F-33-2-0-0-149 (Archival box - standard 33-27)
  - Agenda support papers 3/4. Apr. 1970, F-33-2-0-0-150 (Archival box - standard 33-27)
  - Agenda support papers 4/4. Apr. 1970, F-33-2-0-0-151 (Archival box - standard 33-27)
  - Agenda support papers 1/4. May 1970, F-33-2-0-0-152 (Archival box - standard 33-27)
  - Agenda support papers 2/4. May 1970, F-33-2-0-0-153 (Archival box - standard 33-27)
  - Agenda support papers 3/4. May 1970, F-33-2-0-0-154 (Archival box - standard 33-28)
  - Agenda support papers 4/4. May 1970, F-33-2-0-0-155 (Archival box - standard 33-28)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. June 1970, F-33-2-0-0-156 (Archival box - standard 33-28)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. June 1970, F-33-2-0-0-157 (Archival box - standard 33-28)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. June 1970, F-33-2-0-0-158 (Archival box - standard 33-28)
  - Agenda support papers 1/5. July 1970, F-33-2-0-0-159 (Archival box - standard 33-28)
  - Agenda support papers 2/5. July 1970, F-33-2-0-0-160 (Archival box - standard 33-28)
  - Agenda support papers 3/5. July 1970, F-33-2-0-0-161 (Archival box - standard 33-29)
  - Agenda support papers 4/5. July 1970, F-33-2-0-0-162 (Archival box - standard 33-29)
  - Agenda support papers 5/5. July 1970, F-33-2-0-0-163 (Archival box - standard 33-29)
  - Agenda support papers (special meetings). July 29, Aug. 16, 1970, F-33-2-0-0-164 (Archival box - standard 33-29)
  - Agenda support papers 1/8. Aug. 1970, F-33-2-0-0-165 (Archival box - standard 33-29)
  - Agenda support papers 2/8. Aug. 1970, F-33-2-0-0-166 (Archival box - standard 33-29)
  - Agenda support papers 3/8. Aug. 1970, F-33-2-0-0-167 (Archival box - standard 33-29)
  - Agenda support papers 4/8. Aug. 1970, F-33-2-0-0-168 (Archival box - standard 33-29)
  - Agenda support papers 5/8. Aug. 1970, F-33-2-0-0-169 (Archival box - standard 33-30)
  - Agenda support papers 6/8. Aug. 1970, F-33-2-0-0-170 (Archival box - standard 33-30)
  - Agenda support papers 7/8. Aug. 1970, F-33-2-0-0-171 (Archival box - standard 33-30)
  - Agenda support papers 8/8. Aug. 1970, F-33-2-0-0-172 (Archival box - standard 33-30)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). Sept. 11, 1970, F-33-2-0-0-173 (Archival box - standard 33-30)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Sept. 1970, F-33-2-0-0-174 (Archival box - standard 33-30)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Sept. 1970, F-33-2-0-0-175 (Archival box - standard 33-30)
  - Agenda support papers. Oct. 1970, F-33-2-0-0-176 (Archival box - standard 33-30)
  - Agenda support papers. Nov. 1970, F-33-2-0-0-177 (Archival box - standard 33-31)
  - Agenda support papers. Dec. 1970, F-33-2-0-0-178 (Archival box - standard 33-31)
  - Agenda support papers. Jan. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-179 (Archival box - standard 33-31)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Feb. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-180 (Archival box - standard 33-31)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Feb. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-181 (Archival box - standard 33-31)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Mar. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-182 (Archival box - standard 33-31)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Mar. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-183 (Archival box - standard 33-31)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Apr. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-184 (Archival box - standard 33-32)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Apr. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-185 (Archival box - standard 33-32)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Apr. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-186 (Archival box - standard 33-32)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. May 1971, F-33-2-0-0-187 (Archival box - standard 33-32)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. May 1971, F-33-2-0-0-188 (Archival box - standard 33-32)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. May 1971, F-33-2-0-0-189 (Archival box - standard 33-32)
  - Agenda support papers (special meetings). June 3 and 13, 1971, F-33-2-0-0-190 (Archival box - standard 33-33)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. June 1971, F-33-2-0-0-191 (Archival box - standard 33-33)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. June 1971, F-33-2-0-0-192 (Archival box - standard 33-33)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. June 1971, F-33-2-0-0-193 (Archival box - standard 33-33)
  - Agenda support papers 1/7. July 1971, F-33-2-0-0-194 (Archival box - standard 33-33)
  - Agenda support papers 2/7. July 1971, F-33-2-0-0-195 (Archival box - standard 33-33)
  - Agenda support papers 3/7. July 1971, F-33-2-0-0-196 (Archival box - standard 33-33)
  - Agenda support papers 4/7. July 1971, F-33-2-0-0-197 (Archival box - standard 33-33)
  - Agenda support papers 5/7. July 1971, F-33-2-0-0-198 (Archival box - standard 33-34)
  - Agenda support papers 6/7. July 1971, F-33-2-0-0-199 (Archival box - standard 33-34)
  - Agenda support papers 7/7. July 1971, F-33-2-0-0-200 (Archival box - standard 33-34)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). July 28, 1971, F-33-2-0-0-201 (Archival box - standard 33-34)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). Aug. 6, 1971, F-33-2-0-0-202 (Archival box - standard 33-34)
  - Agenda support papers 1/14. Aug. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-203 (Archival box - standard 33-34)
  - Agenda support papers 2/14. Aug. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-204 (Archival box - standard 33-34)
  - Agenda support papers 3/14. Aug. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-205 (Archival box - standard 33-34)
  - Agenda support papers 4/14. Aug. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-206 (Archival box - standard 33-35)
  - Agenda support papers 5/14. Aug. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-207 (Archival box - standard 33-35)
  - Agenda support papers 6/14. Aug. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-208 (Archival box - standard 33-35)
  - Agenda support papers 7/14. Aug. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-209 (Archival box - standard 33-35)
  - Agenda support papers 8/14. Aug. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-210 (Archival box - standard 33-35)
  - Agenda support papers 9/14. Aug. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-211 (Archival box - standard 33-35)
  - Agenda support papers 10/14. Aug. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-212 (Archival box - standard 33-35)
  - Agenda support papers 11/14. Aug. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-213 (Archival box - standard 33-36)
  - Agenda support papers 12/14. Aug. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-214 (Archival box - standard 33-36)
  - Agenda support papers 13/14. Aug. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-215 (Archival box - standard 33-36)
  - Agenda support papers 14/14. Aug. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-216 (Archival box - standard 33-36)
  - Agenda support papers. Sept. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-217 (Archival box - standard 33-36)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Oct. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-218 (Archival box - standard 33-36)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Oct. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-219 (Archival box - standard 33-37)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Nov. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-220 (Archival box - standard 33-37)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Nov. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-221 (Archival box - standard 33-37)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Dec. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-222 (Archival box - standard 33-37)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Dec. 1971, F-33-2-0-0-223 (Archival box - standard 33-37)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). Jan. 5, 1972, F-33-2-0-0-224 (Archival box - standard 33-37)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Jan. 1972, F-33-2-0-0-225 (Archival box - standard 33-38)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Jan. 1972, F-33-2-0-0-226 (Archival box - standard 33-38)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Feb. 1972, F-33-2-0-0-227 (Archival box - standard 33-38)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Feb. 1972, F-33-2-0-0-228 (Archival box - standard 33-38)
  - Agenda support papers. Mar. 1972, F-33-2-0-0-229 (Archival box - standard 33-38)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Apr. 1972, F-33-2-0-0-230 (Archival box - standard 33-38)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Apr. 1972, F-33-2-0-0-231 (Archival box - standard 33-39)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). Apr. 12, 1972, F-33-2-0-0-232 (Archival box - standard 33-39)
  - Agenda support papers. May 1972, F-33-2-0-0-233 (Archival box - standard 33-39)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. June 1972, F-33-2-0-0-234 (Archival box - standard 33-39)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. June 1972, F-33-2-0-0-235 (Archival box - standard 33-39)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. July 1972, F-33-2-0-0-236 (Archival box - standard 33-39)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. July 1972, F-33-2-0-0-237 (Archival box - standard 33-39)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Aug. 1972, F-33-2-0-0-238 (Archival box - standard 33-39)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Aug. 1972, F-33-2-0-0-239 (Archival box - standard 33-40)
  - Agenda support papers. Sept. 1972, F-33-2-0-0-240 (Archival box - standard 33-40)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). Sept. 25, 1972, F-33-2-0-0-241 (Archival box - standard 33-40)
  - Agenda support papers. Oct. 1972, F-33-2-0-0-242 (Archival box - standard 33-40)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Nov. 1972, F-33-2-0-0-243 (Archival box - standard 33-40)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Nov. 1972, F-33-2-0-0-244 (Archival box - standard 33-40)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Dec. 1972, F-33-2-0-0-245 (Archival box - standard 33-40)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Dec. 1972, F-33-2-0-0-246 (Archival box - standard 33-41)
  - Agenda support papers. Jan. 1973, F-33-2-0-0-247 (Archival box - standard 33-41)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). Jan. 24, 1973, F-33-2-0-0-248 (Archival box - standard 33-41)
  - Agenda support papers. Feb. 1973, F-33-2-0-0-249 (Archival box - standard 33-41)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Mar. 1973, F-33-2-0-0-250 (Archival box - standard 33-41)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Mar. 1973, F-33-2-0-0-251 (Archival box - standard 33-41)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). Mar. 14, 1973, F-33-2-0-0-252 (Archival box - standard 33-41)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Apr. 1973, F-33-2-0-0-253 (Archival box - standard 33-41)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Apr. 1973, F-33-2-0-0-254 (Archival box - standard 33-42)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Apr. 1973, F-33-2-0-0-255 (Archival box - standard 33-42)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. May 1973, F-33-2-0-0-256 (Archival box - standard 33-42)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. May 1973, F-33-2-0-0-257 (Archival box - standard 33-42)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. May 1973, F-33-2-0-0-258 (Archival box - standard 33-42)
  - Chairman/Board Ratification Material. June 1973, F-33-2-0-0-259 (Archival box - standard 33-43)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. July 1973, F-33-2-0-0-260 (Archival box - standard 33-43)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. July 1973, F-33-2-0-0-261 (Archival box - standard 33-43)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3 (includes special meeting Sep. 12). Aug. 1973, Sept. 12, 1973, F-33-2-0-0-262 (Archival box - standard 33-43)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Aug. 1973, F-33-2-0-0-263 (Archival box - standard 33-43)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Aug. 1973, F-33-2-0-0-264 (Archival box - standard 33-43)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Sept. 1973, F-33-2-0-0-265 (Archival box - standard 33-44)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Sept. 1973, F-33-2-0-0-266 (Archival box - standard 33-44)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Nov. 1973, F-33-2-0-0-267 (Archival box - standard 33-44)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Nov. 1973, F-33-2-0-0-268 (Archival box - standard 33-44)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Dec. 1973, F-33-2-0-0-269 (Archival box - standard 33-44)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Dec. 1973, F-33-2-0-0-270 (Archival box - standard 33-44)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Dec. 1973, F-33-2-0-0-271 (Archival box - standard 33-44)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Jan. 1974, F-33-2-0-0-272 (Archival box - standard 33-45)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Jan. 1974, F-33-2-0-0-273 (Archival box - standard 33-45)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Jan. 1974, F-33-2-0-0-274 (Archival box - standard 33-45)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Feb. 1974, F-33-2-0-0-275 (Archival box - standard 33-45)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Feb. 1974, F-33-2-0-0-276 (Archival box - standard 33-45)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Feb. 1974, F-33-2-0-0-277 (Archival box - standard 33-45)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Mar. 1974, F-33-2-0-0-278 (Archival box - standard 33-46)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Mar. 1974, F-33-2-0-0-279 (Archival box - standard 33-46)
  - Agenda support papers 1/4. Apr. 1974, F-33-2-0-0-280 (Archival box - standard 33-46)
  - Agenda support papers 2/4. Apr. 1974, F-33-2-0-0-281 (Archival box - standard 33-46)
  - Agenda support papers 3/4. Apr. 1974, F-33-2-0-0-282 (Archival box - standard 33-46)
  - Agenda support papers 4/4. Apr. 1974, F-33-2-0-0-283 (Archival box - standard 33-46)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). Apr. 23, 1974, F-33-2-0-0-284 (Archival box - standard 33-46)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. May 1974, F-33-2-0-0-285 (Archival box - standard 33-47)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. May 1974, F-33-2-0-0-286 (Archival box - standard 33-47)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. May 1974, F-33-2-0-0-287 (Archival box - standard 33-47)
  - Agenda support papers 1/4. June 1974, F-33-2-0-0-288 (Archival box - standard 33-47)
  - Agenda support papers 2/4. June 1974, F-33-2-0-0-289 (Archival box - standard 33-47)
  - Agenda support papers 3/4. June 1974, F-33-2-0-0-290 (Archival box - standard 33-47)
  - Agenda support papers 4/4. June 1974, F-33-2-0-0-291 (Archival box - standard 33-47)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. July 1974, F-33-2-0-0-292 (Archival box - standard 33-48)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. July 1974, F-33-2-0-0-293 (Archival box - standard 33-48)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Aug. 1974, F-33-2-0-0-294 (Archival box - standard 33-48)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Aug. 1974, F-33-2-0-0-295 (Archival box - standard 33-48)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Aug. 1974, F-33-2-0-0-296 (Archival box - standard 33-48)
  - Agenda support papers. Sept. 1974, F-33-2-0-0-297 (Archival box - standard 33-48)
  - Agenda support papers. Oct. 1974, F-33-2-0-0-298 (Archival box - standard 33-49)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Nov. 1974, F-33-2-0-0-299 (Archival box - standard 33-49)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Nov. 1974, F-33-2-0-0-300 (Archival box - standard 33-49)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Dec. 1974, F-33-2-0-0-301 (Archival box - standard 33-49)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Dec. 1974, F-33-2-0-0-302 (Archival box - standard 33-49)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Dec. 1974, F-33-2-0-0-303 (Archival box - standard 33-49)
  - Agenda support papers. Jan. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-304 (Archival box - standard 33-50)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Feb. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-305 (Archival box - standard 33-50)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Feb. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-306 (Archival box - standard 33-50)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Mar. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-307 (Archival box - standard 33-50)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Mar. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-308 (Archival box - standard 33-50)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Mar. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-309 (Archival box - standard 33-50)
  - Agenda support papers 1/5. Apr. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-310 (Archival box - standard 33-51)
  - Agenda support papers 2/5. Apr. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-311 (Archival box - standard 33-51)
  - Agenda support papers 3/5. Apr. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-312 (Archival box - standard 33-51)
  - Agenda support papers 4/5. Apr. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-313 (Archival box - standard 33-51)
  - Agenda support papers 5/5. Apr. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-314 (Archival box - standard 33-51)
  - Agenda support papers 1/6. May 1975, F-33-2-0-0-315 (Archival box - standard 33-51)
  - Agenda support papers 2/6. May 1975, F-33-2-0-0-316 (Archival box - standard 33-51)
  - Agenda support papers 3/6. May 1975, F-33-2-0-0-317 (Archival box - standard 33-52)
  - Agenda support papers 4/6. May 1975, F-33-2-0-0-318 (Archival box - standard 33-52)
  - Agenda support papers 5/6. May 1975, F-33-2-0-0-319 (Archival box - standard 33-52)
  - Agenda support papers 6/6. May 1975, F-33-2-0-0-320 (Archival box - standard 33-52)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). June 9, 1975, F-33-2-0-0-321 (Archival box - standard 33-52)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. June 1975, F-33-2-0-0-322 (Archival box - standard 33-52)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. June 1975, F-33-2-0-0-323 (Archival box - standard 33-52)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. June 1975, F-33-2-0-0-324 (Archival box - standard 33-53)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. July 1975, F-33-2-0-0-325 (Archival box - standard 33-53)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. July 1975, F-33-2-0-0-326 (Archival box - standard 33-53)
  - Agenda support papers 1/4. Aug. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-327 (Archival box - standard 33-53)
  - Agenda support papers 2/4. Aug. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-328 (Archival box - standard 33-53)
  - Agenda support papers 3/4. Aug. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-329 (Archival box - standard 33-53)
  - Agenda support papers 4/4. Aug. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-330 (Archival box - standard 33-54)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Sept. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-331 (Archival box - standard 33-54)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Sept. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-332 (Archival box - standard 33-54)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). Oct. 7, 1975, F-33-2-0-0-333 (Archival box - standard 33-54)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Oct. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-334 (Archival box - standard 33-54)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Oct. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-335 (Archival box - standard 33-54)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Oct. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-336 (Archival box - standard 33-54)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Nov. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-337 (Archival box - standard 33-55)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Nov. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-338 (Archival box - standard 33-55)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Nov. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-339 (Archival box - standard 33-55)
  - Agenda support papers 1/4. Dec. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-340 (Archival box - standard 33-55)
  - Agenda support papers 2/4. Dec. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-341 (Archival box - standard 33-55)
  - Agenda support papers 3/4. Dec. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-342 (Archival box - standard 33-55)
  - Agenda support papers 4/4. Dec. 1975, F-33-2-0-0-343 (Archival box - standard 33-55)
  - Agenda support papers. Jan. 1976, F-33-2-0-0-344 (Archival box - standard 33-56)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). Feb. 3, 1976, F-33-2-0-0-345 (Archival box - standard 33-56)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Feb. 1976, F-33-2-0-0-346 (Archival box - standard 33-56)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Feb. 1976, F-33-2-0-0-347 (Archival box - standard 33-56)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Mar. 1976, F-33-2-0-0-348 (Archival box - standard 33-56)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Mar. 1976, F-33-2-0-0-349 (Archival box - standard 33-56)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Mar. 1976, F-33-2-0-0-350 (Archival box - standard 33-56)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Apr. 1976, F-33-2-0-0-351 (Archival box - standard 33-57)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Apr. 1976, F-33-2-0-0-352 (Archival box - standard 33-57)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Apr. 1976, F-33-2-0-0-353 (Archival box - standard 33-57)
  - Agenda support papers. May 1976, F-33-2-0-0-354 (Archival box - standard 33-57)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. June 1976, F-33-2-0-0-355 (Archival box - standard 33-57)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. June 1976, F-33-2-0-0-356 (Archival box - standard 33-57)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. June 1976, F-33-2-0-0-357 (Archival box - standard 33-57)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Aug. 1976, F-33-2-0-0-358 (Archival box - standard 33-58)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Aug. 1976, F-33-2-0-0-359 (Archival box - standard 33-58)
  - Agenda support papers. Sept. 1976, F-33-2-0-0-360 (Archival box - standard 33-58)
  - Agenda support papers. Oct. 1976, F-33-2-0-0-361 (Archival box - standard 33-83)
  - Agenda support papers. Nov. 1976, F-33-2-0-0-362 (Archival box - standard 33-83)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Dec. 1976, F-33-2-0-0-363 (Archival box - standard 33-83)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Dec. 1976, F-33-2-0-0-364 (Archival box - standard 33-83)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Feb. 1977, F-33-2-0-0-365 (Archival box - standard 33-84)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Feb. 1977, F-33-2-0-0-366 (Archival box - standard 33-84)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Feb. 1977, F-33-2-0-0-367 (Archival box - standard 33-84)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Mar. 1977, F-33-2-0-0-368 (Archival box - standard 33-84)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Mar. 1977, F-33-2-0-0-369 (Archival box - standard 33-84)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Mar. 1977, F-33-2-0-0-370 (Archival box - standard 33-84)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Apr. 1977, F-33-2-0-0-371 (Archival box - standard 33-85)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Apr. 1977, F-33-2-0-0-372 (Archival box - standard 33-85)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Apr. 1977, F-33-2-0-0-373 (Archival box - standard 33-85)
  - Board retreat. Apr. 1977, F-33-2-0-0-374 (Archival box - standard 33-85)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. May 1977, F-33-2-0-0-375 (Archival box - standard 33-85)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. May 1977, F-33-2-0-0-376 (Archival box - standard 33-85)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. May 1977, F-33-2-0-0-377 (Archival box - standard 33-86)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. June 1977, F-33-2-0-0-378 (Archival box - standard 33-86)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. June 1977, F-33-2-0-0-379 (Archival box - standard 33-86)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. June 1977, F-33-2-0-0-380 (Archival box - standard 33-86)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. July 1977, F-33-2-0-0-381 (Archival box - standard 33-86)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. July 1977, F-33-2-0-0-382 (Archival box - standard 33-86)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Aug. 1977, F-33-2-0-0-383 (Archival box - standard 33-87)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Aug. 1977, F-33-2-0-0-384 (Archival box - standard 33-87)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Aug. 1977, F-33-2-0-0-385 (Archival box - standard 33-87)
  - Agenda support papers. Sept. 1977, F-33-2-0-0-386 (Archival box - standard 33-87)
  - Agenda support papers (special meetings). Sept. 19, 21, 1977, F-33-2-0-0-387 (Archival box - standard 33-87)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Oct. 1977, F-33-2-0-0-388 (Archival box - standard 33-87)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Oct. 1977, F-33-2-0-0-389 (Archival box - standard 33-59)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Nov. 1977, F-33-2-0-0-390 (Archival box - standard 33-59)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Nov. 1977, F-33-2-0-0-391 (Archival box - standard 33-59)
  - Agenda support papers - Harper hearing before Board. Dec. 6, 7, 12, 1977, F-33-2-0-0-392 (Archival box - standard 33-59)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Dec. 1977, F-33-2-0-0-393 (Archival box - standard 33-59)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Dec. 1977, F-33-2-0-0-394 (Archival box - standard 33-59)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Jan. 1978, F-33-2-0-0-395 (Archival box - standard 33-59)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Jan. 1978, F-33-2-0-0-396 (Archival box - standard 33-60)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Jan. 1978, F-33-2-0-0-397 (Archival box - standard 33-60)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Feb. 1978, F-33-2-0-0-398 (Archival box - standard 33-60)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Feb. 1978, F-33-2-0-0-399 (Archival box - standard 33-60)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Apr. 1978, F-33-2-0-0-400 (Archival box - standard 33-60)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Apr. 1978, F-33-2-0-0-401 (Archival box - standard 33-60)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. May 1978, F-33-2-0-0-402 (Archival box - standard 33-61)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. May 1978, F-33-2-0-0-403 (Archival box - standard 33-61)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). May 29, 1978, F-33-2-0-0-404 (Archival box - standard 33-61)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. June 1978, F-33-2-0-0-405 (Archival box - standard 33-61)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. June 1978, F-33-2-0-0-406 (Archival box - standard 33-61)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. July 1978, F-33-2-0-0-407 (Archival box - standard 33-61)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. July 1978, F-33-2-0-0-408 (Archival box - standard 33-61)